moderndonor.com 2008-03-09

# Modern Donor

About Us  
Become a Sponsor  
Privacy Policy  
**Privacy Policy**

We take your privacy seriously at **Modern Donor**. This statement describes our Privacy Policy for our web site, and for the distribution list for **Modern Donor**. 

**Personal Information and Security**

We neither collect nor store any information of a purely personal nature: i.e. home address (unless it is also a business address), telephone or fax numbers, interests, family members, memberships, etc. For online transaction purposes, we ask our clients to provide credit card information, but this is always done in a secure environment. We have implemented industry-accepted encryption processes for the transmission of credit card information, to help keep the information secure, accurate, current and complete. 

**Information we Gather and Retain**

* Business Email addresses to deliver the following to our readers: issues of **Modern Donor** ; promotional information from our _Supporting Sponsors_ ; and information concerning workshops, seminars and meetings of interest to people actively involved as managers and development professionals in the nonprofit sector. 
* Business mail addresses and secure credit card information to enable commercial transactions with Member/Subscribers to the **Modern Donor** , seminar and workshop registrants, and book buyers. 
* Geographic business address information and nonprofit sector and sub-sector information to help our editorial staff plan and direct the content of our publications in an appropriately balanced fashion. 
* Aggregate reader click-through data for articles in **Modern Donor** to help us direct our editorial coverage to areas in which there is the greatest interest. 
* Aggregate reader click-through data for Supporting Sponsors’ logos in **Modern Donor** to help them measure the value of their involvement in this sector information service. 

**Cookies**

A ‘Cookie’ is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. You can set your browser to alert you to the fact that you are about to receive a Cookie, which allows you to choose whether or not to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off Cookies. This, however, will inhibit your useable access to, and operation of, some sections of some web sites. 

We may, on occasion, use ‘Cookies’ to collect anonymous information from visits to our web site to help us deliver a more effective and efficient information service. The trends and statistics that we extract from this information will always be in the aggregate, and of a global nature to help us more effectively direct our editorial content to meet the needs of our readers. 

**Disclosure to third parties**

We will only share personally identifiable information with a third party if and when the individual submitting this information has permitted and directed us to do so, or if we are required by law to do so. As of the last update of this statement, this has not occurred. 

**Links to Other Web Sites**

Our web site contains links to other web sites. **Modern Donor** , **Judith Nichols** , **Jim Hilborn** and **The Hilborn Group Ltd** are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such web sites. 

**Notification of Changes**

This privacy statement was last updated on September 26, 2005.
